

- Syedhashimh675@gmail.com
- +923144103691
- % Linkedin:SHashimHussain
- Shahdara,Lahore

### **OBJECTIVE**

Short-term (This year):

Complete Master's Degree in Software Engineering at Virtual University of Pakistan, enhancing proficiency in Unity Game Engine and developing at least two playable game prototypes.

Long-term (In the next 3-5 years):

I dream of working as a Game Developer at Tencent. I want to help make amazing games and use my skills to come up with new ideas that make gaming even more fun for players everywhere.

### **SKILLS**

Language:

English, Urdu

Computer:

Microsft Office,

**Development**:

HTML/CSS, UNITY, ANDROID STUDIO

#### **INTERESTS**

Passionate about gaming, both as a player and a creator

Constantly exploring new game design concepts. Experimenting with game mechanics to enhance gameplay experiences.

Improving skills in Unity Game Engine to bring game ideas to life.

# HASHIM HUSSAIN

Unity Development 2D/3D

### **EDUCATION**



2018 - 2020

Computer Science

BS Software Engineering from Virtual University of Pakistan

2020 - NOW

Android Game Development

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Game Developer, Self-Employed

2022 - NOW

Currently working on multiple game projects independently using Unity Game Engine.

Managing all aspects of the game development lifecycle, including concept idea, coding, testing, and deployment.

Private School in Shahdara, Computer Teacher

2020 - 2020

Utilized my computer knowledge and skills to teach Secondary Level students as a Computer Teacher.